const contest_1_2 =
    [
        {
            "S/N": 1,
            "Has Preamble": "No",
            "Preamble Text": null,
            "Question": "Find the self-inductance of an air-cored cylindrical solenoid of volume $5.0 \\times 10^{-4} \\mathrm{~m}^{3}$ which is wound with 1200 turns per meter.",
            "Question has figure": "No",
            "Question figure name": null,
            "Answer has figure": "No",
            "Answer figure name": null,
            "Answer": "$9.0 \\times 10^{-4} \\mathrm{H}$\n$$\nL=\\mu_{0} n^{2} V=4 \\pi \\times 10^{-7} H m^{-1} \\times\\left(1200 \\mathrm{~m}^{-1}\\right)^{2} \\times 5.0 \\times 10^{-4} \\mathrm{~m}^{3}=9.0 \\times 10^{-4} \\mathrm{H}\n$$",
            "calculations present": "Yes",
            "Subject": "Physics",
            "Topic Tag": ["Self-Inductance", "Electromagnetism"]
        },
        {
            "S/N": 2,
            "Has Preamble": "No",
            "Preamble Text": null,
            "Question": "Find the work done by an ideal gas in an isobaric process at $200 \\mathrm{kPa}$ in which the volume of the gas changes from $2 \\mathrm{~m}^{3}$ to $1 \\mathrm{~m}^{3}$.",
            "Question has figure": "No",
            "Question figure name": null,
            "Answer has figure": "No",
            "Answer figure name": null,
            "Answer": "$-200 k J$\n$$\nW=P \\Delta V=200 k P a \\times\\left(1 m^{3}-2 m^{3}\\right)=-200 k J\n$$",
            "calculations present": "Yes",
            "Subject": "Physics",
            "Topic Tag": ["Work Done by Gas", "Thermodynamics"]
        },
        {
            "S/N": 3,
            "Has Preamble": "No",
            "Preamble Text": null,
            "Question": "Two springs each of spring constant $5 \\mathrm{Nm}^{-1}$ are connected in parallel. Find the energy stored by the parallel springs when stretched by a $4 N$ force.",
            "Question has figure": "No",
            "Question figure name": null,
            "Answer has figure": "No",
            "Answer figure name": null,
            "Answer": "$0.8 \\mathrm{~J}$\n$$\nU=F^{2} / 4 k=(4 N)^{2} /\\left(4 \\times 5 N m^{-1}\\right)=0.8 \\mathrm{~J}\n$$",
            "calculations present": "Yes",
            "Subject": "Physics",
            "Topic Tag": ["Energy Stored in Springs", "Mechanics"]
        },
        {
            "S/N": 4,
            "Has Preamble": "No",
            "Preamble Text": null,
            "Question": "What is the function of a moderator in a Nuclear Reactor?",
            "Question has figure": "No",
            "Question figure name": null,
            "Answer has figure": "No",
            "Answer figure name": null,
            "Answer": "It slows down neutrons in order that the chain reaction in a nuclear reactor is sustained.",
            "calculations present": "No",
            "Subject": "Physics",
            "Topic Tag": ["Moderator Function", "Nuclear Physics"]
        },
        {
            "S/N": 5,
            "Has Preamble": "No",
            "Preamble Text": null,
            "Question": "Define the term Derived Units.",
            "Question has figure": "No",
            "Question figure name": null,
            "Answer has figure": "No",
            "Answer figure name": null,
            "Answer": "They are units obtained by combining SI base units.",
            "calculations present": "No",
            "Subject": "Physics",
            "Topic Tag": ["Derived Units", "Measurement"]
        },
        {
            "S/N": 6,
            "Has Preamble": "No",
            "Preamble Text": null,
            "Question": "Compare and contrast the nitrogens in an amine and in an amide.",
            "Question has figure": "No",
            "Question figure name": null,
            "Answer has figure": "No",
            "Answer figure name": null,
            "Answer": "In an amine, the nitrogen is bonded to one or two or three alkyl or aryl groups but in an amide, the nitrogen is bonded to at least one carbonyl carbon.",
            "calculations present": "No",
            "Subject": "Chemistry",
            "Topic Tag": ["Amine vs Amide", "Organic Chemistry"]
        },
        {
            "S/N": 7,
            "Has Preamble": "No",
            "Preamble Text": null,
            "Question": "Solve the equation $8 x^{-2 / 3}=2 / 9$",
            "Question has figure": "No",
            "Question figure name": null,
            "Answer has figure": "No",
            "Answer figure name": null,
            "Answer": "$x=216$\n$\\left[x^{-2 / 3}=1 / 36, x^{2 / 3}=36, x^{1 / 3}=6, x=6^{3}=216\\right]$",
            "calculations present": "Yes",
            "Subject": "Mathematics",
            "Topic Tag": ["Solving Equations", "Algebra"]
        },
        {
            "S/N": 8,
            "Has Preamble": "No",
            "Preamble Text": null,
            "Question": "Two events $A$ and $B$ are disjoint with $P(A)=1 / 3$ and $P(A \\cup B)=8 / 15$. Find $P(B)$.",
            "Question has figure": "No",
            "Question figure name": null,
            "Answer has figure": "No",
            "Answer figure name": null,
            "Answer": "$1 / 5$\n$[P(A \\cup B)=P(A)+P(B), P(B)=8 / 15-1 / 3=(8-5) / 15=3 / 15=1 / 5]$",
            "calculations present": "Yes",
            "Subject": "Mathematics",
            "Topic Tag": ["Probability", "Statistics"]
        },
        {
            "S/N": 9,
            "Has Preamble": "No",
            "Preamble Text": null,
            "Question": "Find a unit vector perpendicular to the given vector $\\mathbf{a}=-\\mathbf{6 i}+\\mathbf{8 j}$",
            "Question has figure": "No",
            "Question figure name": null,
            "Answer has figure": "No",
            "Answer figure name": null,
            "Answer": "$(4 \\mathbf{i}+3 \\mathbf{j}) / 5$, (accept also $-(4 \\mathbf{i}+3 \\mathbf{j}) / 5)$\n$[b=\\mathbf{8 i}+\\mathbf{6} \\mathbf{j}$ is perpendicular to $a$, unit vector is $(\\mathbf{8} \\mathbf{i}+\\mathbf{6 j}) / 10=(\\mathbf{4} \\mathbf{i}+\\mathbf{3 j}) / 5]$",
            "calculations present": "Yes",
            "Subject": "Mathematics",
            "Topic Tag": ["Unit Vector", "Vector Algebra"]
        },
        {
            "S/N": 10,
            "Has Preamble": "No",
            "Preamble Text": null,
            "Question": "Which of the following is the largest single membrane-bound intracellular compartment?\na) Ribosome\nb) Golgi apparatus\nc) Nucleus\nd) Endoplasmic reticulum",
            "Question has figure": "No",
            "Question figure name": null,
            "Answer has figure": "No",
            "Answer figure name": null,
            "Answer": "d) Endoplasmic reticulum",
            "calculations present": "No",
            "Subject": "Biology",
            "Topic Tag": ["Cellular Components", "Cell Biology"]
        },
        {
            "S/N": 11,
            "Has Preamble": "No",
            "Preamble Text": null,
            "Question": "Which organ in mammals produces urea?",
            "Question has figure": "No",
            "Question figure name": null,
            "Answer has figure": "No",
            "Answer figure name": null,
            "Answer": "Liver",
            "calculations present": "No",
            "Subject": "Biology",
            "Topic Tag": ["Urea Production", "Mammalian Physiology"]
        },
        {
            "S/N": 12,
            "Has Preamble": "No",
            "Preamble Text": null,
            "Question": "What name is given to the digestion of a cell's own component?",
            "Question has figure": "No",
            "Question figure name": null,
            "Answer has figure": "No",
            "Answer figure name": null,
            "Answer": "Autophagy",
            "calculations present": "No",
            "Subject": "Biology",
            "Topic Tag": ["Cell Digestion", "Cell Biology"]
        }
    ]

export default contest_1_2